<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>100 artifacts on Spencer Chang</title><link>https://www.spencerchang.me/experiments/100posts/</link><description>Recent content in 100 artifacts on Spencer Chang</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 09 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.spencerchang.me/experiments/100posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>58 - perception</title><link>https://www.spencerchang.me/experiments/100posts/perception/</link><pubDate>Sun, 26 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.spencerchang.me/experiments/100posts/perception/</guid><description>People&amp;rsquo;s perception of you hinges so much based on your outer appearance. If you wear flamboyant clothes, you&amp;rsquo;re &amp;ldquo;out there.&amp;rdquo; If you&amp;rsquo;re wearing khakis and hiking boots, you really value comfort, and if you&amp;rsquo;re insistent on thin layers in freezing weather, you value fashion over comfort. These are all common stereotypes that people draw from a single glance, and it can take over your entire impression of a stranger. I&amp;rsquo;ve been thinking about this recently because I got my ears pierced yesterday and because of that, I feel like not only my friends but the strangers around me, even more so, are perceiving me differently.</description></item><item><title>57 - arc of the valley</title><link>https://www.spencerchang.me/experiments/100posts/arc-of-the-valley/</link><pubDate>Sat, 25 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.spencerchang.me/experiments/100posts/arc-of-the-valley/</guid><description>Arc of the valley from Rick, basically the hero&amp;rsquo;s journey but in silicon valley ^421b9d
Bright eyed on the ideals and optimism Disillusionment encountered at the dissonance Deep disillusionment, cynical about everything Matured state of making a difference where you can in your realm of control. Leaving the playground better than you found it The true cynicism comes from dealing with nasty people and artificial problems and finding out that a lot of the promises made around social good are empty.</description></item><item><title>56 - privilege of dreams</title><link>https://www.spencerchang.me/experiments/100posts/privilege-of-dreams/</link><pubDate>Fri, 24 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.spencerchang.me/experiments/100posts/privilege-of-dreams/</guid><description>From a conversation with a friend: i&amp;rsquo;m also sensing a strong the system is broken vibes around money and having privilege to follow your dreams.. the guy she&amp;rsquo;s casually seeing wants to be a full-time writer and has the monetary means to make it happen. The dynamic around privilege to chase your dreams and having to abide by capitalism can feel very overwhelming. I feel like a lot of people around my age are wrestling with the question of capitalism and what it makes us want to do.</description></item><item><title>55 - irreplaceable</title><link>https://www.spencerchang.me/experiments/100posts/irreplaceable/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.spencerchang.me/experiments/100posts/irreplaceable/</guid><description>Thinking about the fact that coda wouldn&amp;rsquo;t be the same if a coworker didn&amp;rsquo;t join, which implies a level of irreplaceability. Being irreplaceable means your value is infinite in our world of supply and demand, as long as the demand is there for what you provide. But the simple fact of being irreplaceable doesn&amp;rsquo;t always coincide with what is needed in the moment or for the long-term. Being irreplaceable has a wide range of meaning.</description></item><item><title>54 - life is fragile</title><link>https://www.spencerchang.me/experiments/100posts/life-is-fragile/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.spencerchang.me/experiments/100posts/life-is-fragile/</guid><description>Life is fragile is a message from Sex Education (fire tv show btw).
The main message is to live for the day because from the hour you’re born you begin to die. Another flavor of live to minimize regrets. We have such limited time on the planet. Don&amp;rsquo;t waste it on people or things that don&amp;rsquo;t make you happy or don&amp;rsquo;t care about you, and cherish the people and things who do because losing them will be incredibly hard.</description></item><item><title>53 - compliments</title><link>https://www.spencerchang.me/experiments/100posts/compliments/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.spencerchang.me/experiments/100posts/compliments/</guid><description>rising lights shining
bright. reaching out beyond the
high, of second sky
that idea about compliments compliments are free energy i actually wrote about in a previous entry on kindness journals, which is wild because it means this experiment is proving its use by giving me a trail of my mental exploration.
This is the 53rd installment in my experiment of publishing raw, lightly edited mini-essays every day towards achieving 100 public pieces.</description></item><item><title>52 - cafe encounter</title><link>https://www.spencerchang.me/experiments/100posts/cafe-encounter/</link><pubDate>Sun, 19 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.spencerchang.me/experiments/100posts/cafe-encounter/</guid><description>Talked to people at Stable Cafe today.
met betty and anton there and chatted them up a lot started because i gave compliment about the DIY jacket to betty, wild how a simple step can result in such a cool connection and conversation anton is super cool. STEAM education curriculum, spiral for french government and international school. Grew up on french island but is italian and was a robotics engineer.</description></item><item><title>51 - extraction and flower</title><link>https://www.spencerchang.me/experiments/100posts/extraction-and-flower/</link><pubDate>Sat, 18 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.spencerchang.me/experiments/100posts/extraction-and-flower/</guid><description>at second sky, gave one of my flowers to a random guy who hit on me. Reminded by how our smallest acts can make the biggest difference.
i&amp;rsquo;m doing &amp;ldquo;fun&amp;rdquo; things with friends but a lot of the time it&amp;rsquo;s not actually in the moment fulfilling for me? like I only need these really stereotypically &amp;ldquo;fun&amp;rdquo; things in small dosages depending on my current mood. For example, I&amp;rsquo;m about to go to porter robinson&amp;rsquo;s second sky music festival, but I actually want to stay in and read about techno-optimism and exploring the relationship between software and people.</description></item><item><title>50 - formulation</title><link>https://www.spencerchang.me/experiments/100posts/formulation/</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.spencerchang.me/experiments/100posts/formulation/</guid><description>I&amp;rsquo;ve been really loving George Saunders recently, and I ran into this interview with him and now love him even more because of his perspective:
I don’t know that it [the ending] was the right one. But I think it was the most interesting one. That’s a funny thing about writing stories. We have that illusion that we are “deciding” what to make a character do, in order to “convey our message” or something like that.</description></item><item><title>49 - now's focus</title><link>https://www.spencerchang.me/experiments/100posts/nows-focus/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.spencerchang.me/experiments/100posts/nows-focus/</guid><description>thinking for 100posts that I stop sending everyone an email all the time just send them weekly updates to be less? Good opportunity for me to summarize how I&amp;rsquo;m feeling too and review my writing. start this week?
discovered dk today who did a public journaling thing with Road to Ramen to document his journey to get enough money from the tools he made that he could survive on ramen. This is sort of what I was aiming at with 100posts, but it keeps ending up feeling like more pressure since I&amp;rsquo;m notifying everyone on my list.</description></item><item><title>48 - singular purpose</title><link>https://www.spencerchang.me/experiments/100posts/singular-purpose/</link><pubDate>Tue, 14 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.spencerchang.me/experiments/100posts/singular-purpose/</guid><description>when&amp;rsquo;s the last time I pursued something with singular purpose that wasn&amp;rsquo;t my career? You know those people who really know what they want and they go after it with everything they got and then they seize it and manifest it. I want to manifest the life that I want. manifest is a good theme for next year. What would I choose to pursue with a singular purpose right now? Is it being a good writer?</description></item></channel></rss>