<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Spencer Chang</title><link>https://www.spencerchang.me/</link><description>Recent content on Spencer Chang</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 24 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.spencerchang.me/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Decoding your Mind</title><link>https://www.spencerchang.me/posts/decoding-your-mind/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.spencerchang.me/posts/decoding-your-mind/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Discovering a New Year</title><link>https://www.spencerchang.me/posts/discovering/</link><pubDate>Sun, 23 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.spencerchang.me/posts/discovering/</guid><description>Exploration—the relinquishing of the old for something new and unknown. Why do we explore? What drives us to leave behind cozy homes, comfortable routines, and familiar lands, foods, and faces to seek out the new and unknown?</description></item><item><title>Opening the Lid on the Workspace Black Box</title><link>https://www.spencerchang.me/posts/opening-the-lid/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.spencerchang.me/posts/opening-the-lid/</guid><description/></item><item><title>The Rider</title><link>https://www.spencerchang.me/posts/rider/</link><pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.spencerchang.me/posts/rider/</guid><description>The night was cold and dark. The moon shone brightly, gently singing her graceful hymn. The light didn’t shine very far, however. A thick wall of sinister clouds prevented any escape of the beautiful song below.</description></item><item><title>Sublime Arts</title><link>https://www.spencerchang.me/posts/sublime-arts/</link><pubDate>Tue, 19 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.spencerchang.me/posts/sublime-arts/</guid><description>1:45 am. We had just gotten back from the movies, and I was going through the regular ritual of preparing for my nightly recharge. The room was pitch dark except for the flickering amalgam of multicolored lights dancing across the window: reflections mirroring the revelry of a city alive at night.
As I was finishing my movements in robotic silence, an irregular symphony of beats stirred me from my semi-wakeful, semi-listless state.</description></item><item><title>Rice Fields and Murky Identities</title><link>https://www.spencerchang.me/posts/rice-fields/</link><pubDate>Sun, 06 Oct 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.spencerchang.me/posts/rice-fields/</guid><description>Rice fields right outside 宜梧 (YiWu) Junior High School during sunset (taken on my Nikon D3400)
“来吃饭了！(literally, &amp;lsquo;come eat!&amp;rsquo; but interpreted as &amp;lsquo;food&amp;rsquo;s ready!&amp;rsquo; )” rang through the hallways of my house, emanating from the kitchen. This was a daily occurrence, after a long day of school or work, signaling that dinner, which my 奶奶 (grandma) had lovingly prepared, was ready. Growing up in a Chinese American household, I was lucky to have my grandma live with us; this forced me to learn Mandarin from a young age because she couldn’t speak English.</description></item><item><title>From Student to Teacher</title><link>https://www.spencerchang.me/posts/student-to-teacher/</link><pubDate>Thu, 26 Sep 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.spencerchang.me/posts/student-to-teacher/</guid><description>Photo by Mwesigwa Joel on Unsplash
”誰是我們的老師啊？(Who are our teachers?)“
“是我們 (We are)” I blurted.
Shit. We had just finished a whole week of training where we were specifically told to pretend not to know Chinese to encourage our students to speak English. And I had just responded in Chinese to their question. Great, first minute of “teaching” and I already messed up. How am I gonna survive 2 weeks of this?</description></item><item><title>Stupid Scholars, the Power of Hands, and Free Lunches: Riding Through 4 Years of University</title><link>https://www.spencerchang.me/posts/stupid-scholars/</link><pubDate>Sun, 02 Jun 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.spencerchang.me/posts/stupid-scholars/</guid><description>“It’ll be fine,” I reassured myself for what seemed like the millionth time. The mere prospect of a roller coaster ride had reduced me to a broken record. I’ve never been a follower of the camp that derives thrill, much less joy, from artificial fear. Horror movies are a hard no, especially at night, alone in my room, and maybe it’s obvious, but I had never ridden a roller coaster.</description></item><item><title>Scaling Knowledge Access and Retrieval at Airbnb</title><link>https://www.spencerchang.me/posts/knowledge-graph/</link><pubDate>Tue, 04 Sep 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.spencerchang.me/posts/knowledge-graph/</guid><description/></item></channel></rss>