<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>software on Spencer Chang</title><link>https://www.spencerchang.me/tags/software/</link><description>Recent content in software on Spencer Chang</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 11 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.spencerchang.me/tags/software/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>67 - fast feedback loops and perils of convention</title><link>https://www.spencerchang.me/experiments/100posts/fast-feedback-loops/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.spencerchang.me/experiments/100posts/fast-feedback-loops/</guid><description>I had today off too, so I spent the day eating burritos and making some updates to my personal website. I launched my fits stream the other day and started sharing it publicly while making some usability and performance improvements that this new project exposed. Few improvements included adding a permalink + a quick way to copy that link to clipboard since people were referencing their favorites by the #. On the performance side, I added lazy loading for the images and added some responsive image handling so that the content wasn&amp;rsquo;t reflowing every time a new image loaded.</description></item><item><title>60 - internet of empty promises</title><link>https://www.spencerchang.me/experiments/100posts/internet-of-empty-promises/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.spencerchang.me/experiments/100posts/internet-of-empty-promises/</guid><description>Thinking about link rot and ephemerality of the internet and how even things we have control of (our tools) experience this. We run from one shiny tool to the next and often, things don&amp;rsquo;t carry over or if they do import it&amp;rsquo;s not at full fidelity. Software promised us the permanence and stability that paper has never offered, but apps trapped our information in uncompromising and inflexible cages.
This is the 60th installment in my experiment of publishing raw, lightly edited mini-essays every day towards achieving 100 public pieces.</description></item><item><title>Rituals at Scale: How we remixed templates</title><link>https://www.spencerchang.me/posts/rituals-remixing/</link><pubDate>Thu, 13 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.spencerchang.me/posts/rituals-remixing/</guid><description/></item></channel></rss>