<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>creative on Spencer Chang</title><link>https://www.spencerchang.me/tags/creative/</link><description>Recent content in creative on Spencer Chang</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 16 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.spencerchang.me/tags/creative/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>the gaps</title><link>https://www.spencerchang.me/posts/the-gaps/</link><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.spencerchang.me/posts/the-gaps/</guid><description>thumping beats, reverberating ground a ritualized welcome or a dreadful threat to the entrants strangers and substances a perfect match for forgotten nights and regrettable fights the empty spaces of life those gaps in the space between the lived and the unlivable between the vocalized and the omitted water surges from within to fill those that make us ache with the rhythm of that fateful beat, that make us rage with the hot fury of those substances’ burn I reach out for the spaces yet they reach away an infinite chase, head after tail a still, pristine lake above a single drop triggers the climax below These gaps exist to be reached Yes, we live for reaching but oh!</description></item><item><title>Dilution</title><link>https://www.spencerchang.me/posts/dilution/</link><pubDate>Sun, 06 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.spencerchang.me/posts/dilution/</guid><description>Under my watchful eyes, a weight settles over the world. Thick layers of shadows pile on top of one another until all that’s left poking out in the sea of night are tiny fireflies, little torches signaling life. I look out my golden-ratioed window, a precise, technical masterpiece with a reinforced panel of glass acting as a projector for the production playing out beyond. In the distant horizon, the line where the sky meets the world and the galactic bend, glinting ever so inconspicuously, levels with my eyes.</description></item><item><title>a twinkle</title><link>https://www.spencerchang.me/posts/a-twinkle/</link><pubDate>Sun, 03 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.spencerchang.me/posts/a-twinkle/</guid><description>A shaft of moonlight pierces the curtain
In my concrete abode, a flare lighting the way out
The ephemeral promise draws me
like a firefly I seek my hopes.
The defeaning chorus of cicadas
consumes me in the darkness.
Out in the fields, the grains cultivated
What was promised eclipses the night
A permanent night light bathes me
as the swarm of stars engulfs me
from the infinite black canvas above</description></item><item><title>The Rider</title><link>https://www.spencerchang.me/posts/rider/</link><pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.spencerchang.me/posts/rider/</guid><description>The night was cold and dark. The moon shone brightly, gently singing her graceful hymn. The light didn’t shine very far, however. A thick wall of sinister clouds prevented any escape of the beautiful song below.</description></item><item><title>Sublime Arts</title><link>https://www.spencerchang.me/posts/sublime-arts/</link><pubDate>Tue, 19 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.spencerchang.me/posts/sublime-arts/</guid><description>1:45 am. We had just gotten back from the movies, and I was going through the regular ritual of preparing for my nightly recharge. The room was pitch dark except for the flickering amalgam of multicolored lights dancing across the window: reflections mirroring the revelry of a city alive at night.
As I was finishing my movements in robotic silence, an irregular symphony of beats stirred me from my semi-wakeful, semi-listless state.</description></item></channel></rss>